Guide to the Associated Students of Stanford University Records SC0009
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Legislative, Series 2
  - Senate Meeting File 1976-1977: committee reports (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Senate Meeting File 1976-1977: committee reports (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Senate Meeting File 1976-1977: resolutions and bills, 1976-77 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Senate Meeting File 1976-1977: correspondence, reports, 1976-77 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Senate minutes, agenda, reports, constitution, etc., 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - ASSU Miscellaneous I, 1976-1983 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - ASSU Miscellaneous II, 1976-1983 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Senate File: By-laws of ASSU, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Senate File: Agenda and minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Senate File: Election Commission, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Senate File: President's reports; and Resolution, Bills, and By-laws, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Senate File: Miscellaneous, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Senate Minutes 77/78, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Senate Minutes 77/78, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Senate 1977/78 Minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Senate 1977/78: Constitution, By-laws, and miscellaneous, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Senate Questionnaire, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Senate Orientation Manual, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Senate 1978/79 Minutes, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Senate 1978/79 Minutes, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Senate Agenda, minutes, and other records (1 of 2), 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Senate Agenda, minutes, and other records (2 of 2), 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Senate General Information, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Nominations Committee, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Senate Orientation, 1978-1980 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Nominations Committee, 1977-1982 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Senate 1980-81: memos, reports, agenda, minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Senate 1979/80: correspondence, memos, job descriptions, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Senate 1979/80: Minutes and Agenda, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Senate 1979/80: Minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Senate 1979-80: miscellany, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Senate Issues, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Senate 1979/80: agenda and minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Senate 1979/80: agenda and minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Senate Orientation, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Senate Agenda Packets [agenda and minutes], 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Senate 1980-81: agenda, minutes, miscellany, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Senate Orientation materials, 1980-81 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Senate Orientation materials, 1980-81 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Senate 1981-82 Orientation: Standing Rules, Chart of Procedures, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - ASSU Senate Meetings, Agendas, etc., 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Meeting Minutes (notes)--Senate Chair, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Executive Council Meetings, Information, etc. 81-82, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - ASSU Nominations Committee Info, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - (Senate Minutes) February 22 - April 5, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - (Senate Minutes) April 19 - May 3, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - (Senate Minutes) May 17 - May 18, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - (Senate Minutes) May 24, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - (Senate Minutes) Summer Session June - August 2, 1, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - (Senate Minutes) November 1, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Senate 1983-1984: agenda for Third Meeting July 17 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - 15th SenateAgenda for Meeting June 26, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Senate 1983-84 Rosters/contact lists, meetings:, 1983 May 18-24 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Senate 1983-84 Rosters/contact lists, meetings:, 1983 Aug.-Sept (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Senate 1983-84 Minutes and documents for meeting of, 1983 Sept. 27 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Senate 1983-84 meetings:, 1983 October (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Senate 1983-84 Minutes and documents for meeting of, 1983 Nov. 8 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Senate 1983-84 meetings:, 1983 November (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Senate 1983-84 Minutes and documents for meeting of, 1983 Nov. 29 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Senate 1983-84 meetings:, 1984 January (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Senate 1983-84 meetings:, 1984 January (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Senate 1983-84 Meetings:, 1984 Feb. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Senate 1983-84 Meetings:, 1984 March-April (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Senate 1983-84 Miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Senate 1983-1984 meetings:, 1984 Feb. 14 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Senate 1983-1984 meetings:, 1984 Feb. 14 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Senate 1983-1984 meetings:, 1984 Feb. 28 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Senate 1983-1984 meetings:, 1984 March 6 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Senate 1983-1984 meetings:, 1984 March 6 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Senate 1983-1984 meetings:, 1984 April 10 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Senate 1983-1984 meetings:, 1984 April 24 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Senate 1983-1984 meetings:, 1984 April 24 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Senate 1983-1984 meetings:, 1984 May 10 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Senate 1983-1984 meetings:, 1984 May 22 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Senate 1983-1984 meetings:, 1984 May 22 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Senate 1983-1984 committee meeting information, 1980-84 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Minutes and related information of the XIVth Senate (1 of 2), 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - XIVth Senate, minutes and related information (1 of 2), 1983 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Minutes and related information of the XIVth Senate (2 of 2), 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - XIVth Senate, minutes and related information (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - XVth Senate Agenda Packets (1 of 3), 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - XVth Senate Agenda Packets (2 of 3), 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - XVth Senate Agenda Packets (3 of 3), 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - XVth Senate 14th Meeting minutes, etc., (1 of 3), 1985 Feb. 15 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - XVth Senate 14th Meeting minutes, etc., (2 of 3), 1985 Feb. 15 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - XVth Senate 14th Meeting minutes, etc., (3 of 3), 1985 Feb. 15 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - XVI Senate Agendas and Minutes, 1985 May (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - XVI Senate Agendas and Minutes, 1985 June and July (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - XVI Senate Agendas and Minutes, 1985 September (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - XVI Senate Agendas and Minutes, 1985 October (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - XVI Senate Agendas and Minutes, 1985 November (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - XVI Senate Agendas and Minutes, 1986 January (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - XVI Senate Agendas and Minutes, 1986 February (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - XVI Senate Agendas and Minutes, 1986 March (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - XVI Senate Agendas and Minutes, 1986 April (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Senate Elections, 1986 Spring (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Senate Orientation meeting (XVII Senate candidates), 1986 April (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - XVI Senate Agendas and Minutes, 1986 May 6 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - XVI Senate Agendas and Minutes, 1986 May 20 and 27 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - XVII Senate-Elect meeting, 1986 May (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - XVII Senate first meeting, 1986 May 28 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - ASSU Senate agenda for, 1987 Feb. 24 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - ASSU Senate agenda for, 1987 March 3 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - ASSU Senate agenda for, 1988 Jan. 26 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - ASSU Senate agenda (and minutes) for, 1988 Feb. 23 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - ASSU Senate agenda for, 1988 March 1 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - ASSU Senate agenda for, 1988 April 5 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - ASSU Senate agenda for, 1988 May 3 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Appropriations Committee, 1983-1988 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Student Affairs, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - ASSU Senate agenda for, 11/17/88 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - ASSU Senate agenda for, 12/1/88 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Special Allocations Senate Bills, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Administration and Rules Committee, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - ASSU Senate agenda for, 4/6/89 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - XX Senate, 1st Meeting, 1989 June 1 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - XX Senate, 2nd Meeting, 1989 Sept. 20 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Appropriations Committee, 1989 Oct. 2 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Education, Research, and Residences committee, 1989 Oct. 3 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Student Affairs Committee Meeting Minutes, 1989 Oct. 3 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Budget and Finance Committee Meeting, 1989 Oct. 5 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - XX Senate, 3rd Meeting, 1989 Oct. 10 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Appropriations Committee, 1989 Oct. 17 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - XX Senate, 4th Meeting, 1989 Oct. 24 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Education, Research, and Residences, 1989 Oct. 30 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Student Affairs Committee Meeting Minutes, 1989 Oct. 31 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Appropriations Committee, 1989 Nov. 7 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - XX Senate, 5th Meeting [Agenda packet], 1989 Nov. 9 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Education, Research, and Residences committee, 1989 Nov. 9 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Budget and Finance Committee Meeting, 1989 Nov. 9 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - XX Senate, 6th Meeting [includes agenda packet with minutes from 5th meeting], 1989 Nov. 21 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - XX Senate, 7th Meeting, 1989 Dec. 3 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - XX Senate, 8th Meeting, 1990 Jan. 16 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Budget and Finance Committee Meeting, 1990 Jan. 23 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - XX Senate, 9th Meeting, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Appropriations Committee 1/26 and 2/9, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - XX Senate, 10th Meeting, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - XX Senate, 11th Meeting, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - XX Senate, 12th Meeting, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Education, Research, and Residences [ERR] minutes, Mar. 5, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - XX Senate, 13th Meeting, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Education, Research, and Residences[ERR] minutes 4/12 and 5/19, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - XX Senate, 14th Meeting, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - XX Senate, 15th Meeting, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - XX Senate, 16th Meeting, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Budget, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Minutes of the XXIth Senate, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - ASSU Senate agenda for, 3/7/91 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - ASSU Senate agenda for, 5/16/91 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - ASSU Senate agenda for, 5/28/91 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - ASSU Senate agenda for, 10/22/91 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Elections 1890s, 1893-1899 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Elections 1900s, 1910s, 1900-1912 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Elections 1930s, 1935 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - ASSU Senate Elections and ballot, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Senate Campaign Material, undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - ASSU Elections, flyers from the mid-1970s (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Elections Review Board Minutes--Senate, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Senate Elections Review Board Minutes - second hearing, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Senate Elections Review Board Minutes, 1977 Nov. 17 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Elections Review Board Report, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Elections Review Board Correspondence, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Elections Review Board Report, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Democracy in Disarray: The Failures of Stanford's Student Government: A Study of Events and Causes and A Call for Structural Change: Report of the 1977-78 ASSU Election Review Board (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - ASSU Elections ‘81-'82, 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - ASSU Elections Report, 1982-1984 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Elections, 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - ASSU Documents--Campaign Practices Code, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - ASSU: Daily articles, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - ASSU Elections pt. 1, 1974-1982 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - ASSU Elections pt. 2, 1974-1982 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Election Handbooks, 1977-1985 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Election Handbooks, 1993-1995 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - ASSU Elections miscellaneous, 1971-1978 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - ASSU Election Handbook Spring 1998 (2 copies) (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Election flyers CRAP [Committee to Retire Aspiring Politicos], undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Handbook of Student Control, 1914-1916 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Fund. Standard and Honor Code Misc., 1914-1978 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - ASSU Judicial Council, Men's and Women's Council, 1916-1971 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Honor Code Posters, 1931 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Honor Code--history, Student Liquor Laws, 1946-1980 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Honor Code and Fundamental Standard, 1955-1963 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Fundamental Standard and Honor Code Booklets ASSU, 1955-1976 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Honor Code, 1960-1979 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Judicial procedures, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Temporary Judicial Council, 1965-1968 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Judicial System, 1965-1968 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Judicial System, 1966-1976 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Judicial Committees, 1968-1982 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Judicial System, 1969-1970 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Judicial System, 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Student Conduct Legislative Council, 1971-1983 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Proposed revisions of the Judicial charter, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Student Conduct Legislative Council, 1973-1979 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Judicial System, 1974-1976 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Student Judicial Committee, 1974-1976 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Honor Code Surveys, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Student Judicial Committee 1976-1977, 1976-1982 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Stanford Judicial Council, 1978-1979 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Stanford Judicial Council Candidates, 1982-1983 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Original ASSU Constitution. Handwritten, "found in the basement of Assembly Hall" final pages missing, 1891-1895 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Constitution of the Associated Students of Leland Stanford Jr. University [booklets], 1896-1907 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Constitution and By-Laws of Associated Students of Stanford University (includes Associated Women Students and Women's Athletic Association), 1930-1939 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Constitution and By-Laws of Associated Students of Stanford University [booklets], 1940-1947 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Constitution, By-Laws, By-Laws of Boards 1949-1950 and 1952-1953; By-Law Changes, Amendments to ASSU Constitution Spring Quarter 1950 to Winter Quarter 1951, 1949-1952 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Constitution and By-laws of the Associated Students of Stanford University 1959-60, 1959-1960 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Constitution and By-laws of the Associated Students of Stanford University 1960-61, 1960-1961 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Constitution and By-Laws of the ASSU 1955-56 to 1960-61 [bound volume], 1955-1961 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Constitution and By-laws of the Associated Students of Stanford University 1961-62, 1961-1962 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Constitution and By-laws of the Associated Students of Stanford University 1962-63, 1962-1963 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Constitution and By-laws of the Associated Students of Stanford University 1963-64, 1963-1964 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Constitution and By-laws of the Associated Students of Stanford University 1964-65, 1964-1965 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Constitution and By-Laws of the ASSU 1961-62 to 1963-64 [bound volume], 1961-1964 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Constitution and By-Laws of the ASSU 1965-1966 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Master Budget 1966-1967; Constitution and By-laws, possibly in revision, undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - ASSU Constitution and By-Laws, 1965-1966 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - By-Laws, typed verison, circa 1963 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Complete for 1965-1966 ASSU Constitution, By-Laws, and the Standing Rules of Official Organizations, including the ASSU Budget (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Constitution and By-Laws of the ASSU 1961-62 to 1964-65 [bound volume], 1961-1965 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - ASSU Constitution and By-Laws, 1966-1967 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Constitution and By-laws of the Associated Students of Stanford University 1967-1968 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Constitution Revision 1968 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Constitution and By-laws of the Associated Students of Stanford University 1968-1969 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Constitution and By-laws of the Associated Students of Stanford University 1968-1969 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Constitution and By-laws of the Associated Students of Stanford University 1968-1969 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - ASSU Constitution as of January 1969, V.P. copy (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Constitution of the Associated Students of Stanford University (2 copies), 1969 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Constitution Revision, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Constitution - Amendments, 1965-1969 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Constitution and By-Laws of the Associated Students of Stanford University [undated], circa 1965 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Constitution and By-Laws of the Associated Students of Stanford University, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - ASSU Constitution and By-laws, Senate, 1970-1971 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - ASSU Senate 1971-1972 - Constitution and By-laws (re amendments) (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - By-laws and amendments, 1972-1973 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - By-Laws of the Associated Students of Stanford University, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - By-Laws of the Associated Students of Stanford University, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - By-Laws of the Associated Students of Stanford University, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - By-Laws of the Associated Students of Stanford University, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Amendments ‘70-'75, 1968-1975 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - ASSU Constitution and Organization, 1975-1976 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - By-laws and constitution, 1977-1978 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - By-Laws of the Associated Students of Stanford University, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - By-Laws of the Associated Students of Stanford University, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Constitution and By-Laws, 1977-1979 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Constitutional Correspondence, 1970-1979 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Proposed ASSU charter [undated], circa 1975 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Constitution and By-Laws of the Associated Students of Stanford University, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - ASSU Constitution general information, 1973-1981 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Constitution and By-Laws of the ASSU; Rules of Order and Standing Rules of the Association Senate, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - ASSU Correspondence, 1967-1975 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - ASSU Constitution, 1955-1983 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - ASSU Letters of Acceptance, 1969-1971 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - ASSU Relationship with University, 1970-1975 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Senate Correspondence 11/72-6/74, Rocky Barber/Reggie Turner, 1972-1974 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - ASSU General Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence re: ASSU, 1981-1982 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - ASSU General Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - ASSU Senate Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Executive Committee Minutes Oct. 2, 1924-June 6, 1928, 1924-1928 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee Minutes Oct. 2, 1928-May 27, 1931, 1928-1931 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee Minutes 1931-1933 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee Minutes 1933-1937 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee Minutes Oct. 5, 1937-June 6, 1939, 1937-1939 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee Minutes Oct. 1939-June 1941, 1939-1941 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee Minutes Sep. 30, 1941-Aug. 25, 1942, 1941-1942 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee Minutes Sep. 30, 1942-Aug. 18, 1943, 1942-1943 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee Minutes Oct. 13, 1943-Aug. 30, 1944, 1943-1944 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee Minutes 1944-45, 1944-1945 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee Minutes 1945-46, 1945-1946 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee Minutes 1946-47, 1946-1947 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee Minutes 1947-48, 1947-1948 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee Minutes 1948-49, 1948-1949 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee Minutes 1949-50, 1949-1950 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee Minutes Jun. 28, 1950-May 31, 1951, 1950-1951 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee Minutes 1951-1952 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee Minutes Jun. 25, 1952-May 27, 1953, 1952-1953 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee Minutes 1953-54, 1953-1954 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee Minutes 1954-55, 1954-1955 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Legislature Minutes 1955-1956 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Legislature Minutes 1956-1957 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Legislature Minutes 1957-1958 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Legislature Minutes 1959-1960 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Legislature Minutes 1958-1959 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Legislature Minutes 1960-1961 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Legislature Minutes 1961-1962 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Legislature Minutes 1962-1963 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Legislature Minutes 1963-1964 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Legislature Minutes 1965-1966 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Legislature Minutes 1966-1967 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Financial Legislation: Excerpts from Legislature Minutes, 1963-1964 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Senate Agendas, Minutes, Treasury Info, 1970-1971 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Legislation passed, 1983-1984 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Concert Nework, charter, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Committee of Fifteen (C-15) Proposal, 1970-1973 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - C-15 Proposal 1974-75, 1974-1975 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Chinese Students' Issue [support of students in China], 1989 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - XXth Senate, agenda and minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - ASSU assorted records, some on investment responsibility, 1977-1991 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Senate Interns, 1979-1980 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - ASSU Senate Finance Committee, 1976-1982 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Action records, Tom Huseby, 6/24/71, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - ASSU Elections and Fee Assessments - clippings, 1979-1982 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - ASSU Honor Code volume, 1916-1949 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    Bound volume contains correspondence, reports, various papers on the topic presented to campus groups, questionnaires, transcripts of two panel discussions arranged by the Men's and Women's Councils 1936, clippings, and other materials.
- Student Manager, Series 3
  The Student Manager records consist largely of bound volumes of reports from or about various clubs, committees, or events in an academic year. Detailed lists of contents for each volume are included in the listing that follows. Bound student police reports for 1939-1963 are also in this series. The responsibilities of the student police were largely crowd control at campus events; their duties included monitoring behavior, handling tickets, controlling parking and traffic, and keeping out gate crashers. The reports list the student police on duty, sometimes the various tasks, and usually include a paragraph or two on the event itself. Many of the entries are from The Sunday Flicks.
  - Reports of the General Manager of the ASSU, 1924-1925 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Student Manager's Report, 1926-1927 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Associated students; basketball pavilion; circular letters; concert series; contracts; corduroy ball; cotillon-sophomore; debate; dramatic council; Encina Club dances; glee clubs; Irish marathon; junior prom; labor day; military ball; publications; registration dances; skull and snakes jolly-up; senior ball; women
  - Student Manager's Report, 1927-1928 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Associated students; bonfire report; circular letters; charters; concert series; cotillion-sophomore; convalescent home; debate report; Encina Club; Irish marathon; junior prom; men's glee club; military ball; registration dances; senior ball; publications; women; YMCA
  - Student Manager's Report, 1928-1929 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Associated students; bonfire report; circular letter; circle "S"-boxing; concert series; convalescent home; cotillion-sophomore; debate; Encina Club; good will trip; Irish marathon; junior prom; memorandum-letters; men's glee club; military ball; registration dances; senior ball; sigma delta chi; publications; Toyon; women; women's athletic association; YMCA; YWCA